Guide to the Abraham Lincoln Brigade Archives Vertical Files: Individuals ALBA.VF.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: ALBA Individual Files, 1
  - Stark, George Werner (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Steck, Robert (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Steinberg, Jacob (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Stern, Marvin (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Stevenson, Alwyn (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Stewart, Cameron, 1939-: "Summoned to the Eternal Field" (Thesis on ALB) (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Stix, Frederick (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Stojewa, Conrad H. (aka Reuben Barr; Rubin Barr) (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Stoloff, Louis (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Stone, Harold Wilhelm (Torvinen) (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Stone, Hy (aka Herman Hersh) (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Stone, William (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Stout, Frank (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Strachey, John, 1901-1963 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Straus, Mark (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Strauss, Walter (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Strukl, Victor (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Stuart, Yale (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Sugrue, Daniel (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Sullivan, Marty (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Summers, Thane (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Sundstrom, Jose Valentin (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Susman, William (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Swan, Tom (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Swanson, West (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Szurek, Alexander (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Tabb, Herbert L. (Hy) (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Taft, Anne, 1912-1990 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Taine, Wayne J. (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Tanenhaus, Sam (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Tanz, Alfred (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Tapilianos, Steve (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Tapsell, Wally (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Taratzinakis, Demetrios (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Taro, Gerda, 1911-1937 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Taylor, Alan John Percivale, 1906-1990 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Taylor, Daniel Bebe (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Taylor, Douglas (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Taylor, Joseph (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Tenor, Leon (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Thaelmann, Ernst (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Thayer, Don (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Thomas, Fred: "To Tilt at Windmills, a Memoir of the Spanish Civil War" (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Thomas, Hugh (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Thompson, David (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Thompson, Richard Chester (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Thompson, Robert (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Thomson, Godfrey Edward (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Thornton, Mark (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Thornton, Nate (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Thornton, Ralph (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Ticer, Leon Norwell (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Ticer, Raymond Ellis (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Tieger, Rudolph (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Timpson, Arthur (includes memoir) (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Tinker, Frank G. (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Tisa, John (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Titus, William B. (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Tivin, Isidore (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Tobman, Morris (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Todd, Robert Moore (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Toney, Anthony (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Toole, Samuel Coleman (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Torgoff, Leonard Sloan (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Torrance, Alex (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Toub, Howard (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Traynor, Thomas (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Trent, Tom (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Troxel, Steve (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Turner, Bob (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Tyler, Hamilton (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Usera, Vincent (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Valledor, Alvanez, Jose Antonio (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Valuch, Rudolph (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Van der Schelling, Bart (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Van Felix, William (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Veltfort, Theodore "Ted" (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Venta, Paul (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Vercelli, John (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Viamala, Ralph (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Vidali, Vittorie (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Vilar, Angelo (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Vogel, Joseph (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Vogel, Sidney (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Volkas, Bernard (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Voros, Sandor (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Wacksman Sorkin, Rose (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Wagner, Ervin (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Waitzman, Sam (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Wallach, Albert (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Wallach, Harry (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Wallach, Hy (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Wallach, Jesse (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Walsh, Joseph Martin (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Walters, Samuel (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Wardlaw, Ralph (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Warfield, Frank (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Warren, Alvin (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Waters, George Walter (Box 8, Folder 131)
  - Watson, Alonzo Robert (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Watson, Will (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Watt, George, 1913-1994 (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Weinberg, Jerry (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Weiner, Milton (Morris) (Box 8, Folder 136)
  - Weiner, Rose, 1908-1995 (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - Weinerman, Alex (Box 8, Folder 138)
  - Weir, Harry (Box 8, Folder 139)
  - Weisbord, Albert: Writings on Spain (Box 8, Folder 140)
  - Weisenfeld, Nathan (Box 8, Folder 141)
  - Weiss, Jacob (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - Weissman, Irving, 1913-1998 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - Welles, Orson (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - Wellman, Saul (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - Wendkos, Elkan (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - Wendorf, Paul (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Wesson, Neil (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Whalan, Joseph (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - Wheeler, William Gilmore (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - White, David McKelvy, 1901- (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - White, Milton, 1917- (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - White, William Edward (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Whitfield, Frank (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Wickman, Morris (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Wideman, Jefferson (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Wildman, Earl Randall (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Wilkes, Harry (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Wilkinson, Frank: Account of 1936 visit to Spain (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Williams, Fred (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Williams, Paul Elisha (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Willis, Samuel Conway (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Wilson, H.H. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Wimmer, William (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Winsheimer, Lawrence (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Winston, Henry, 1911-1986 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Wirta, Paul (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Witt, Arthur (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Wolf, Nathan (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Wolff, Frieda (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Wolff, Milton (Milt) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Wolff, Milton: World War II letters (copies) (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Wolson, Morton (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Woodfield, Michael (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Workoff, Irving (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Wren, Samuel (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Wrought, Alexander (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Wyden, Peter (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Yasvas, Pasqual (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Yates, James, 1906- (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Yellin, Jack (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Yellin, John (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Yellin, Morris (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Ylikyla, Axel (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Young, Joseph (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Youngblood, Charles (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Zablackas, Vete (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Zajac, Sylvester (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Zak, Steve (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Zalka, Mate (General Lukach) (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Zalon, Sol (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Zalonz, Walter (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Zamares, Joseph (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Zaslovsky, William Boris (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Zawadowski, Joseph (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Zecovic, Milan (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Zeronas, Anton (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Ziagos, John (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Ziegler, Albert (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Zientz, Harry (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Ziffren, Lester (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Zivin, Louis (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Zlatovski, George (includes memoir) (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Zlotnick, Louis (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Zumel, Eufrosimo (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Zykosky, Simon Morris (Box 9, Folder 54)